翻译   国士章鱼X
翻译   杏仁斯嘉丽
翻译   肉松
翻译   吃冰棒
翻译   煮粥
翻译   WalkingNerd
翻译   沫沫
翻译   苏小黛
时间轴   西·查
时间轴   王者葱
时间轴   Jessie
后期   饿得慌
顾问   老杜
校对   草草
总监   草草
纸牌屋
第五季  第七集
汤姆·汉默施密特
《华盛顿先驱报》
肝癌互助小组
安东尼·莫雷蒂纪念基金
如果我们遂了他的愿
If we give him what he wants...
如果我们按厄舍的意思任命法官  那就完了
If we give Usher what he says, his justice, that is it.
彻底完了  我们就被他拿住了
It's over. He owns us.
-别小题大做  -是倒好了
- Don't exaggerate. - I wish I were.
这样的交易你做过上千次了
You've made a thousand deals.
这次不一样
Yeah, well, this one is different.
-怎么不一样  -因为我能感觉到
- Why? - Because I can feel it right here.
-你听见自己在说什么了吗  -清清楚楚
- Do you hear yourself? - Yeah, loud and clear.
我倒有点奇怪你似乎一个字都没听见
I'm a little confused that you don't seem to hear me at all.
只要我们真正夺回权力
Once we're solidly back in power,
-我们就能恢复职位...  -幼稚
- we will regain our position... - That is naive.
你从来没这么幼稚过
Naive is new for you.
我这是现实  不是幼稚
Realistic. Not naive.
我们奋斗的一切成果  都会烟消云散
Everything we've worked for, we can kiss it goodbye.
我们同意让厄舍来挑人  没得商量
We agreed to Usher's pick. It's non-negotiable.
说得太对了  他挑人  他的法官
That's exactly right. It's his pick. It's his justice.
他想控制我们的政府  我们的白宫
He's trying to control our house. The White House.
我向他保证过了  弗兰西斯
I gave him my word, Francis.
你保证
Your word?
你保证  这场谈话真是毫无意义
Your word? This conversation is pointless.
成熟点吧
Grow up!
你以为你是谁
Who do you think you are?
我以为我是临时代总统
I think I am a temporary president
想帮你夺回宝座
trying to get you back in office.
如果你不认为眼下是我们至关重要的关口
And if you don't think that we're at a critical juncture in the road,
那你真是错得可悲
you are pathetically mistaken.
醒醒吧  克莱尔  醒醒吧
Wake up, Claire! Wake up!
这是欧洲东部时间今早
Recorded this morning EET
在大马士革亚默克区拍到的
in the Yarmouk neighborhood of Damascus.
看来他在剑桥期间喜欢上吃巧克力了
Seems he developed a taste for chocolate while at Cambridge.
画面上这位是艾哈迈德·艾哈迈迪
Smiling for the camera is Ahmed Al Ahmadi,
尤瑟夫的兄弟
Yusuf's brother.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
我和尤瑟夫·艾哈迈迪谈了很久
I had a long conversation with Yusuf Al Ahmadi.
他们俩完全不像
They look nothing alike.
就是他
It's him.
艾哈迈德还在我们监控中吗
Is Ahmed still in our sights?
-是的  -这个机会非常难得
- He is. - This is a rare opportunity.
我们应该趁机发动定点袭击
We should seize the moment and make a targeted strike.
-总监  得了吧  -总统女士
- Director, please. - Madam President...
有什么问题吗  将军
Is there some issue, General?
艾哈迈德·艾哈迈迪不可能大老远地
Ahmed Al Ahmadi didn't travel all the way
从他的据点跑到大马士革就为了买糖吃
from his compound to Damascus to buy a candy bar.
他肯定要见什么人  我们应该查清是谁
He's meeting with someone. Let's find out who.
可这样他可能会被我们惊动  就此消失
Unless we're detected, and he disappears for good.
可我们只要等一等
But if we wait,
就非常有可能了解更多哈里发国的情报
there's a huge potential to learn more about ICO.
它的成员  联系人  行动规律和战术
Its members, contacts, habits, tactics.
你今天早上真是一反常态地
You know, you're sounding uncharacteristically dovish
保守啊  将军
this morning, General.
我同意布雷格将军的看法
I agree with General Braegher.
虽然对艾哈迈迪发动精确空袭
While a successful air strike against Ahmadi
-会非常有利于  -这跟选举无关  凯茜
- would play well... - This isn't about the election, Cathy.
当然没关系  我是说  只要我们手段得当
No, of course not. I mean, if we do this correctly,
我们就可以逐步瓦解哈里发国的网络
we can begin the process of dismantling ICO's network.
干掉他
Take him out.
如果总统同意的话
If the president agrees,
我认为这对国家最有利
I think it's the best thing for the country.
我觉得这会给哈里发国发出非常明确的信号
Well, I think it would send a very clear message to ICO.
短期来看没错  但是
In the short term, yes, but...
短期没错就够了
No other term is relevant.
我觉得我们已经在
I think we have been operating
恐怖主义的阴影下忍受太久了
under the shadow of terror for too long.
为了美国人民  我们必须采取坚决行动
For the sake of the American people, we need to act now.
预计需要多长时间  将军
What's the timetable, General?
只要目标位置准确  几个小时就行
For an actionable location, most likely a number of hours.
谢谢
Thank you.
你这是在浪费我们的时间
You're wasting our time.
我们要讲究他在哪以何种面貌出现
We're being selective about where and how he appears.
很快他就什么活动都不能参加了
Soon he won't be at any events at all.
汉娜  我们只是想尽力把他和你送入白宫
Hannal, we're just trying to land him and you in the White House.
不是布洛哈特-康威  马克  是康威在前
And it's not Brockhart-Conway, Mark. It's the opposite.
他肯定忍不了多久
He won't put up with this much longer.
我知道他一定很难受
I know, I'm sure it's hard on him.
我得接这个电话  抱歉
I have to take this. I'm sorry.
他到那儿之后会怎么样
What happens after he gets there?
-威尔会怎么样  -我们会支持他
- To Will? What happens? - We'll be there for him.
-你和布洛哈特将军  -对
- You and General Brockhart? - Yes.
威尔是什么角色
What will Will's role be?
我会继续支持你丈夫
I will continue to support your husband.
给我一个真正的答案  你欠我的
Give me a real answer. You owe me that.
他的角色将是美国总统
His role will be President of the United States.
麦克风还开着  布洛哈特脱口而出
The mic was still hot and Brockhart just kept talking.
-她是这么说的  -抗命吗
- That's what she said. - Insubordination?
-她用的是这个词吗  -她听着是这意思
- That's the word she used? - It's what it sounded like to her.
他在谈士兵  他说
He was talking about soldiers and he said, quote,
"我第一个站出来让军人抗命"
"I'll be the first to tell them not to listen."
-她能不能弄到真正的录音  -是有代价的
- Can she get her hands on the actual clip? - For a price.
-我还以为她是朋友  -对  聪明的朋友
- I thought she was a friend. - Yeah, a smart friend.
这是一条很不错的辩论后30秒广告
It's a nice 30-second spot, post-debate.
如果有辩论的话
If there is a debate.
攻击他们的长处
Hits them at their strength.
动摇他们的军事公信力
Takes the military credibility away.
这种东西能反转大选结果
This is the kind of thing that can turn an election.
不管要付出什么代价  都值了
Whatever this costs... it's worth it.
我们把它搞到手  证实一下
Let's secure it and then verify it.
不管是不是休会任命本森大法官
Recess appointment of Judge Benson or no,
得让人们继续关注田纳西和俄亥俄的重新投票
people need to stay focused on the revote in Tennessee and Ohio
以及我们为何走到这一步
and how the hell we got here.
好
All right.
我让助理安吉拉联系你
I'll have my assistant Angela reach out
看你什么时候需要我去录影棚
to confirm what time you need me at the studio.
好  好的
All right. Yep. Yeah.
我把道格·斯坦普被劫车那天
I collected everything I could find
能查到的资料都搜集齐了
about the day Doug Stamper was carjacked.
好
Good.
好了  那么
All right, so...
是在哪
where was that?
在哪发生的
Where that happened?
在马里兰
In Maryland.
就在
Right around, um...
我是在离那儿半小时车程的地方长大的
Yeah, I grew up about a half an hour from there...
在这里
It's here.
瑞秋·波斯纳的
And Rachel Posner's...
最后已知地址
last known address.
也就15分钟路程
I'd say they were about 15 minutes apart.
我不知道我为什么要跟你解释
I'm not sure why I need to explain myself to you.
你为什么要去国安局
Why would you go to the NSA?
我想调查一名美国公民是否安然无恙
I was inquiring into the well-being of an American citizen.
他就是个心怀不满的黑客而已
He's just a disgruntled hacker.
那你为什么对他这么感兴趣呢
Then why are you so interested in him?
他看上去怎么样
How did he look?
我是为了我自己问的
I'm asking for me.
我13岁就认识艾丹了
I've known Aidan since I was 13 years old.
他和我妈妈曾交往过几年
He and my mom dated for several years.
当然  那是很久之前了
Was a long time ago, obviously.
但他并不想要国安局那份工作
But as far as the NSA job, he didn't want it.
是我逼他接受的
I made him take it.
我不明白他们怎么找到他的  他为什么在那儿
I don't understand how they got him or why he's there.
我需要知道他是安全的
I need to know that he is safe.
他看上去还行
He looked fine.
他知道什么  莉安
What does he know, LeAnn?
也许跟你我知道的差不多
Probably about the same as you and me,
所以我们不能让他惹上严重的麻烦
which is why we need to keep him out of any serious trouble.
我不想涉足你的私生活  莉安
I don't want to get involved in your personal life, LeAnn.
-我是来见总统的  -当然
- I'm here to see the president. - Of course.
但你仔细想想  凯茜
But when you think about it, Cathy,
我们都脱不了干系
we're all sort of involved here.
如果他有危险  他是无法承受的
If he is in any kind of danger, he is not built for it.
你好  凯茜
Hi, Cathy.
简
Jane.
莉安·哈维  简·戴维斯  简是副部长
LeAnn Harvey, Jane Davis. Jane is under secretary--
商务部副助理部长  负责国际贸易
Deputy under secretary of commerce for international trade.
很拗口
It's a mouthful.
很高兴见到你本人
Yeah, it's good to put a face to the voice.
你有布洛芬吗
Uh, do you have any ibuprofen?
-我好像有阿司匹林  -不行
- Oh, I might have some aspirin. - No.
-我过敏  会起疹子  -我们好像有
- I'm allergic. Gives me hives. - We may have some.
你家就是做轮胎的哈维家族  对吧
You're the Harveys of the tire company, yes?
我父亲和叔叔二十年前卖了公司
My father and uncle sold the business 20 years ago.
之后胎面就不一样了
And the treads haven't been the same since.
但很不错  你还是来到了华府
But it's great. You finally landed in D.C.
我会告诉总统你们俩都来了
I'll let the president know you're both here.
谢谢你的药
Uh, thank you for this.
我们对调这两句就行了
Let's just reverse those two sentences and it's there.
切中要点
It's to the point.
-凝练  -没错  凝练
- Pithy. - Yes, pithy.
她们来了
Your meeting is here.
谢谢
Thank you.
本森法官正在前往
And Justice Benson is en route
白宫参与宣布仪式
to the White House for the announcement.
我会让她在黄色椭圆厅等
I'll have her wait in the Yellow Oval.
好  让她们进来  行吗
Uh, great. Can you send the others in, please?
好的
Of course.
前总统也会去玫瑰园吗
Is the former president meeting us in the Rose Garden?
弗兰西斯不去
Francis will not be there.
他不必去
He's not needed.
戴维斯女士
Miss Davis.
杜兰特国务卿
Secretary Durant.
-好久不见  -是啊  上次见面是在哪
- It's been a long time. - Yes, where was that?
阿斯彭一家智库  2000年初
A think tank in Aspen, early 2000.
那时还有很多"智慧的火花"
Oh, there was a lot of thinking happening back then.
还好我们阻止了
I'm glad we put a stop to that.
请坐
Please, have a seat.
我看过了与北京的
So, I've gone over the numbers
钢铁协议的草案数据
of the proposed agreement of steel with Beijing
我有些问题想问你
and I have a couple of questions for you.
总统女士  我们需要带你撤离
Madam President, we need to evacuate you now.
怎么回事
What's going on?
请撤离  总统女士  是紧急情况
Please, Madam President. It's urgent.
女士
Ma'am.
你们要带我去哪
Where are you taking me?
-将您转移到总统紧急行动中心  -为什么
- We're moving you to the PEOC. - Why?
他们会在下面告诉您  女士
They'll brief you down below, ma'am.
弗兰西斯人呢
Where's Francis?
道格·斯坦普呢  还有耶茨先生呢
Where's Doug Stamper? And Mr. Yates?
我们在照章办事  女士
We're following protocol, ma'am.
国家安全顾问卡弗蒂在路上了
National Security Advisor Cafferty is on her way.
-女士  -不  我们等弗兰西斯
- Ma'am? - No, we'll wait for Francis.
他会在里面与您会合
He'll meet you inside.
我们要等弗兰西斯  这是命令
We will wait for Francis. That's an order.
-总统女士  -卡弗蒂女士  怎么回事
- Madam President. - Miss Cafferty, what's going on?
尚无确切消息
Nothing's confirmed yet,
但一辆携带放射性物质的卡车失踪了
but a truck carrying radioactive material has gone missing.
-这是真的吗  -我们得和格林谈谈
- Is this real? - We have to talk to Green.
我们进去吧
Let's head inside.
是
Yes.
我明白了  谢谢
I see. Thank you.
国土安全部收到网络司令部的消息
Homeland received word from Cybercom
一辆携带三台铯137辐照器的卡车
that a truck carrying three cesium-137 irradiators
未按时到达两个检查站
missed two checkpoints.
卡车本该从亚特兰大
It was supposed to be traveling from Atlanta
驶回巴尔的摩的生产厂商那里
back to the manufacturer in Baltimore.
卡车现在在什么位置
Where do we think the truck is now?
卡车的卫星定位下线了
Truck's GPS is offline.
怎么会出这样的破事
How the hell does a thing like that happen?
-我们得重新评估  -可是该重新评估了
- We'll have to reevaluate. - You're damn right we will.
但我们必须作出决定
But we need to make some decisions.
我们应该通知特区警察和弗州州警
We should notify Metro PD and Virginia State Police.
要不要疏散群众
Are we gonna evacuate the public?
不行  在采取任何行动之前
No. Before we do anything,
我要和反恐处局长谈一谈
I wanna speak to the head of counterterrorism.
给我接助理局长格林
Get Assistant Director Green on the line.
-女士  国安部已经  -总统说得对
- Ma'am, Homeland is over... - The president is right.
女士
Ma'am?
我是安德伍德总统
This is President Underwood.
眼下我们还不清楚谁对这起事件负责
At this time, we have no idea who's responsible.
格林局长  我最好还是
Director Green, perhaps it's better
把你接到免提上  请稍等
I patch you into the whole room. One second.
自从他的轮班开始  司机就失联了
The driver's been unreachable since his shift began.
卡车上的放射物
There's enough radiation on that truck
足够影响方圆50公里左右的区域
to impact a 30-mile radius.
即便不被武器化  也会扩散到大气中
Even if it's not weaponized, it would be in the air,
水里  影响儿童和平民
in the water, children, people...
将军  我在这里都能听见车轮轰轰响了
General, I can hear the wheels grinding from here.
最好还是不要妄加推测  先生
I'd rather not speculate, sir.
请你尽情推测一下
Oh, please do.
过去几天以来  哈里发国的情报越来越多
Over the past several days, there has been increased ICO chatter,
但这已经是新常态了
but that is the new normal.
我们把可能受影响区域的地图和数据发过去了
We've sent over stats and maps of potentially affected areas.
我真不知道哪个更可怕
I don't know what's worse.
是随时会炸的脏弹  还是全城人知道
A dirty bomb about to go off or what'll happen to the city
我们在找一枚脏弹后的反应
when they know we're looking for one.
-上头有谁留守  -赛斯和莉安
- Who do we have left upstairs? - Seth and LeAnn.
你和格林保持通信
You stay in touch with Green.
如果真的有脏弹
If this is a dirty bomb,
那局面可就彻底不一样了
then we've just entered a different world.
好  先生
Yes, sir.
好了  我们继续集中力量
All right, we need to stay focused
制定一份紧急疏散计划
on our contingency plan for an evacuation
但不要让外界察觉我们的行动
without the appearance of doing so.
我们需要准备实施单向...
We need to be ready to implement one way...
给我联系能源部的清理小队...
We need to get the cleanup team from the Energy...
...有权调取安保监控录像....
...whose jurisdiction it is to get the security cams...
没错  最终宣布后
Yes. Whenever it happens,
这次任命便能打破最高法院的僵局
this appointment would break the court's deadlock.
我们终于能继续推进这次大选了
And we would get this election going again.
但请大家退一步想一想
But let's step back a minute.
田纳西已经不重要了
Tennessee is out of the equation.
无论谁赢下田州  都不够取胜
Whoever wins that state, it's not enough.
这样就取决于最后一个州  俄亥俄州
It's come down to one state. Ohio.
一个州的选择  将左右
One state is about to choose
下一任美国总统的人选
the next President of these United States.
我们怎么会让这种事发生
How did we let this happen?
而且还不止一次
And it keeps happening.
这届政府一贯喜欢搞闭门政治
This is an administration that operates behind closed doors,
逃避公共监督
out of the public eye.
今天的突然推迟也是一贯的套路
Today's sudden postponement is typical.
玫瑰园没发表一个字的声明
With no announcement in the Rose Garden,
整个白宫也完全没有任何消息放出
and literally zero news coming from the White House,
我们不得不去想  究竟发生了什么幕后惊变
one has to wonder what is going on behind the scenes
才导致这次意外推迟
to cause this unexpected delay.
白宫的沉默  振聋发聩
The silence is deafening.
在这样一场旷日持久
After such a protracted,
令人疑惑  混乱不堪的选举之后
confusing and, frankly, chaotic election,
我们有权了解真相
we deserve clarity.
可是  又是这样
Instead, here we are again...
我们又被蒙在鼓里  神经紧张
left out of the loop and on the edge of our seats.
我希望美国人民不会习惯了这种现象
I just hope America isn't getting used to this.
-喂  -是我
- Hello? - Hey, it's me.
道格
Doug?
为什么没人告诉我
Why wasn't I read in?
-告诉你什么  -正在发生的事
- To what? - Whatever's going on.
如果总统躲入地堡会对我们有利
If this is gonna play for us, the president in the bunker,
我要知道该如何操作
I need to know how to play it.
有一辆运送
There's a truck carrying
放射性物质的货车失联了
radioactive material that's gone missing.
好  赛斯和我要准备一份声明吗
Okay. Should Seth and I prepare a statement?
-我们要说货车在哪  -不清楚
- Where are we saying the truck is? - We don't know.
-什么时候能找到它  -也不清楚
- When are we gonna find it? - We don't know.
等下  真的有事发生吗
Wait, is something really happening?
可能没有
Probably not.
-喂  -可能没有
- Hello? - Probably not?
那我该做些什么
What am I supposed to do?
-是道格吗  -是的
- Is that Doug? - Yeah.
我能跟他说两句吗
Can I talk to him?
-你能告诉我们什么  -表现如常
- Hey, what can you tell us? - Act normal.
继续关注情势
Stay on point.
只回应正在进行的竞选活动
Comment only on the ongoing campaign.
我已经把他们的日程活动延期了
I've already postponed their scheduled events.
我们现在有危险吗
Look, are we in danger here or what?
我无法回答这个问题
I can't answer.
因为我也不知道
Because I don't know.
静等国安部的进一步指示吧
Await further instructions from Homeland.
好吧
All right.
道格  我们还要留在这儿吗
Doug, should we be here?
他挂了
He hung up.
我们在做什么
What are we doing?
诺拉觉得我们需要通知麦卡锡议长
Nora thinks we need to notify Speaker McCarthy.
我觉得现在谈政府继续运作为时尚早
I think it's too soon for a continuity of government.
如果我们计划撤离  需要通知国会
If we're planning an evacuation, Congress needs to be notified--
我说了  我觉得太早了
I said, I believe it is a bit too early.
总统女士  莫里森总监认为...
Madam President, Director Morrison thinks that--
等下  莫里森总监在哪  为什么...
Wait a minute. Where is Director Morrison? Why--
她选择留在国家情报总监办公室
She opted to stay at ODNI.
她在那里指挥行动
She's monitoring from there.
至少给她打个电话
Well, at least let's get her on the phone.
我们早该在数月前趁有机会时铲除哈里发国
We should have wiped out ICO when we had the chance.
我们没问你的个人意见  将军
We didn't ask for your personal opinion, General.
我们需要了解艾哈迈德·艾哈迈迪的最新情况
What we need is an update on the Ahmed Al Ahmadi situation.
是  女士  我这就去和莫里森总监确认
Yes, ma'am. I'll check with Director Morrison now.
我有一些关系
I have contacts, you know.
本地的私人承包商  也许能帮上忙
Private contractors in the region that might be of help.
你是暗示说你的联系人
Are you suggesting that your contacts
比联调局和国安局知道得还多吗
know more than the Bureau, the NSA--
我没有暗示什么
I'm not suggesting anything.
我是在告诉你
I'm telling you.
我认识和哈里发国谈判过的第三方人士
I know third parties that have negotiated with ICO in the past.
人质之类的事  他们也许知道点什么
Hostages and whatnot... who may know something.
但我需要打个电话
But I need a line.
保密电话
Just a... a secure one.
我在这儿都快透不过气了
I can barely breathe in here.
我去给咱们倒杯咖啡
I'm gonna go get us a cup of coffee.
戴维斯女士怎么会有这么高的安全等级
How does Miss Davis have this level of clearance?
这值得探究
That's a good question.
-我们是不是自作自受  -什么
- Did we bring this on ourselves? - What?
-对不起  我不该这么说的  -听我说
- I'm sorry. I shouldn't have. - Listen to me.
我们所做的一切  一切
Everything we've done, everything,
都是我们必须做的
is exactly what we had to do.
我们都还不知道这是不是真的
We don't even know if this is real.
这是我在香港买的
I get these in Hong Kong.
最好喝的速溶咖啡出自环太平洋地区
The best instant coffee comes out of the Pacific Rim.
-你想来一杯吗  -如果你还有多的
- Would you like one? - If you can spare it.
我包里总是装着三四包
Oh, I always have three or four in my bag.
不知我们要在这里待多久
I wonder how long we'll be down here.
目前情势还不明朗
The situation's still unclear.
我不该喝咖啡的  我还有点站不稳
I shouldn't be drinking coffee. I still feel a little shaky.
你看起来还好
You don't look it.
摸摸我的脉搏
Feel my pulse.
我看你很自若
You seem very much in control to me.
你也是
So do you.
这说明了我们什么
What does that say about the two of us?
好的  谢谢
Yes, thank you.
海豹突击队正在追踪艾哈迈德·艾哈迈迪
The SEAL team is on the trail of Ahmed Al Ahmadi,
但是国家情报局认为
but National Intelligence believes
他发现我们在追踪他了
he's discovered we're following him
而那卡车正是对策
and the truck is a countermeasure.
哈里发国想看到艾哈迈迪完好地走出大马士革
ICO wants to see Ahmadi walking out of Damascus in one piece.
如果我们袭击  他们会反攻
If we strike, they will hit back.
需要启动首都撤离程序
Capital-wide evacuation procedures need to be initiated--
-等等  -我们得首要考虑民众
- Just hold on! - No, the public is our priority--
等等  我想知道袭击的可能性有多大
Hold on! I want to know how close we are to a strike
以及这辆该死的卡车在哪里
and where this goddamn truck is
然后我们再做最后的决定
before we make any final decisions.
"我们再做最后的决定"
"We make any decisions"?
没错  我仍然是
Yes, I am still in a position to make--
如果我错了就纠正我  但你不是
Correct me if I'm wrong, but you are not in a position--
诺拉  敌人不在这里
Nora. The enemy isn't in here.
卡弗蒂说得对  我们应该撤离
Cafferty is right. We should evacuate.
但我想的是将军
But it's the general who's on my mind.
卡弗蒂女士
Miss Cafferty.
我完全失态了  请接受我的道歉
I was entirely out of line. Please accept my apology.
我和戴维斯谈过了
I spoke with Davis.
-怎样  -一无所获  她只是在耍滑头
- And? - Nothing. She was just flexing.
凯茜
Cathy.
今天是谁安排了和克莱尔的会议
Who called a meeting with Claire today?
你还是戴维斯女士
You or Miss Davis?
是简
Jane did.
非常感谢  凯茜
Thank you very much, Cathy.
-没事了吗  -是的  谢谢
- Was that all? - Yes, thank you.
抱歉  还有一件事
Oh, sorry, one more thing.
布雷格什么时候得到第四颗星的  哪届政府
When did Braegher get his fourth star? Which administration?
几届前
A couple back.
他和布洛哈特是一起的吗
So he and Brockhart together?
是的  还有几位也在大概同一时期晋升
And a few others who were elevated around the same time, yes.
谢谢  凯茜
Thank you, Cathy.
我们谈过的那个布洛哈特的料  你拿到了吗
That Brockhart spot we talked about. You have it?
证实了吗
Is it verified?
等等
Hold on.
好了
Ready.
我对天发誓
I swear to God,
要是安德伍德往边境派兵
if Underwood puts soldiers on those borders,
我第一个站出来让军人抗命
I'll be the first to tell them not to listen.
如果美国总统下达那种命令
If the President of the United States gives orders like that,
你就让他早死早超生
you put him out of his misery.
没了  这是全部
That's it. That's all I have.
不  这很好
No, that's good.
如果我们撑过了今天
If we survive the day.
赛斯还和你在办公室吗
Is Seth still in the office with you?
我在总统办公室  坐在坚决桌后
I'm in the Oval, sitting behind the Resolute desk.
你不会的
That's not you.
你总是对我下判断
You know, you keep deciding who I am
却总是误判我
and you keep reading me wrong.
有关于这里发生了什么的谣言吗
Are there rumors about what's going on down here?
有  但我们在应付了
Yes, but we're deflecting.
-康威竞选团队来问过吗  -还没有
- Has the Conway campaign reached out? - Not yet.
将军在俄亥俄州做巡回宣传  州长断联了
The general's on a stump in Ohio and the governor's off the grid.
-好的  继续留意他  -我会的
- Okay. Stay on him. - I will.
除非是世界末日  那就没关系了
Unless it's the end of the world and it doesn't matter.
再见  道格·斯坦普
Goodbye, Doug Stamper.
你确定你该进去那里吗  金发姑娘
Are you sure you should be in there, Goldilocks?
你还好吗
Are you all right?
坦白说  我在想我们在地下多深
Honestly, I was thinking about how far down we are
以及我不喜欢这样
and how it's not my favorite thing.
对不起  你需要进来吗
I... I'm sorry. Do... do you need to be in here?
不不  没关系
No. No, no. It's fine.
我曾经害怕飞行  后来克服了
I used to have a fear of flying, but I got over it.
现在再也不怕了
Doesn't bother me at all anymore.
但我的恐惧似乎转向了另一个方向
But the pendulum seems to have swung the other way.
如果我想太多  会开始有活埋感
If I think too hard, I start to feel buried.
不好意思  室内空气循环让我更加不安了
Forgive me. It's the recirculated air, makes things worse.
戴维斯女士  你为什么会来这儿
Miss Davis, why are you here?
-特勤局带我来的  -不
- This is where the Secret Service led me. - No.
不管是否在准入名单上  你必定是自愿来的
Access list or not, you have to choose to be here.
我总是选择最安全的地方
I always choose the safest place.
你为什么会来这儿
Why are you here?
感觉有机可寻
It felt like an opportunity.
会面的机会  私下会面
A chance for a meeting, not quite on the books.
我刚通完电话  总统女士
I just got off the phone, Madam President.
我有来自国外私人承包商的信息
I have information from abroad, from private contractors...
艾哈迈迪在大马士革
Ahmadi is in Damascus.
多方势力竞相要捉住他
And a number of parties were racing to capture him,
其中当然包括美国
including, of course, the United States.
但是没有人
But no one...
能在今天逮住他
will be capturing him today.
或是在选举前逮住他
Or before the election.
我的职业
I've made a career...
就是处理世界的问题地区
out of dealing with problematic parts of the world.
我的工作  就是想象不可想象之事
It's kind of my vocation to imagine the unimaginable.
失陪了
Excuse me.
-抱歉  -抱歉
- Pardon me. - I'm sorry.
-没事  -失陪了  总统先生
- It's all right. - Excuse me, Mr. President.
我感觉她想把艾哈迈迪献给我们
I had the distinct feeling she was offering Ahmadi to us.
意思是
Meaning?
她说有多方势力正在设法捉住他
She said there are a number of groups looking to capture him,
但在选举之前都不会有人成功
but that no one will. Not today or before the election.
这是我们自找的
We brought this on ourselves.
-我们逼得太紧  -我们存活下来了
- We pushed too hard. - We've survived.
-我们自我孤立了  弗兰西斯  -又如何
- We isolated ourselves, Francis. - So what?
你我都明白一件
We both know something
其他人拒绝承认的事
the rest of the world refuses to acknowledge.
世上没有正义  唯有征服
There is no justice, only conquest.
我告诉你  我们要是准许他们疏散华盛顿
And let me tell you, we let them evacuate D.C.,
我们就没戏了 克莱尔  我们就输了
we are done, Claire. We've lost.
请进
Yes?
我刚和莉安通了话  你们得听听
I just spoke to LeAnn. You need to hear this.
我对天发誓
I swear to God,
要是安德伍德往边境派兵
if Underwood puts soldiers on those borders,
我第一个站出来让军人抗命
I'll be the first to tell them not to listen.
如果美国总统下达那种命令
If the President of the United States gives orders like that,
你就让他早死早超生
you put him out of his misery.
让我出去
Let me out.
-很抱歉  先生  我不能...  -开门
- I'm sorry, sir. I'm not allowed-- - Open the door.
-我奉命...  -我已经不是总统
- My orders are to-- - I am no longer the president.
我已无义务或责任在身  是不是
I have no responsibilities or obligations. Isn't that correct?
解除威胁前我们不能让你出去
We can't send you above until the threat is contained--
-把门打开  -让他出去
- Open this door. - Let him out.
-女士  -让总统出去
- Ma'am? - Let the president out.
把门打开
Open the door.
打开
Open it.
总统女士
Ma'am.
我们必须开始疏散
We need to initiate evacuation now.
不  将军  我说疏散才疏散
No, General. We'll do it when I say so.
真的很抱歉
I'm really sorry.
我知道我答应你了  但我得去接我小孩
I know I agreed to do this, but I have to go pick up my kids.
没事  要不我搭你的车
Okay. Well, what if I just rode in the car with you?
家长都在互相发信息
You know, parents are texting one another.
其中一位家长在国安局任职
One of them works at the NSA
他认为有恐袭的可能  所以...
and he thinks there's a terror threat, so...
这事以前也发生过  但...世事难料
I mean, this has happened before, but you just... You never know.
我母亲上个月肾衰竭过世了
My mom died of kidney failure last month.
我很遗憾
Oh, I'm so sorry.
她在候捐名单上吗
Uh, was she on the donor list?
有  但排得不够靠前
Yeah, but not close enough to the top.
你介意吗  我们可以边走边说
Do you mind? You could talk while we walk out of here.
好吧  好
Sure. Yeah.
安东尼病了多久了
Uh, how long was Anthony sick for?
大概两年
About two years.
他一直在抗争  非常顽强  直到最后
And he fought it hard. So hard. The entire way.
这地方  只要是现金支付  我就不多问
This unit, if they pay cash, I don't ask questions.
-但你记得那两个年轻女子吧  -当然
- But you remember these young women? - Yeah, of course.
她们非常亲密  如果你明白我的意思
They were very close, if you know what I mean.
但她们很可爱
But they were sweet.
那你有没有见过这个人
And did you ever see... this man?
我不清楚究竟是怎么回事
Look, I don't know what was going on here.
但你认得他吧
But you recognize him?
认得
Yeah. Okay?
是有一个长这样的人预付了三个月房租
Someone looking like him paid the rent. Three months, up-front.
但我说了  我不做评判
But like I said, I don't judge.
我不明白你问的是什么  总统先生
I'm not sure what you're asking, Mr. President.
得了吧
Oh, please.
某个人或者某些人
Someone or someones...
今天想把我和我夫人困在地下
tried to make my wife and I lose the election
好让我们输掉大选
by keeping us underground today.
我想知道你对此有什么了解
And I would like to know what you know about that.
我们都在实时应对
We've all been responding in real time
一起潜在的恐怖袭击
to a potential terrorist attack.
但你选择待在这里
But you chose to stay here.
你怎么不和我们一起去地堡
Why weren't you in the bunker with us?
我选择留在我的办公室
I chose to remain in my office
监督对艾哈迈德·艾哈迈迪的逮捕或击杀
to oversee the capture or killing of one Ahmed Al Ahmadi.
但今天上午  你和布雷格将军
And yet there was great tension this morning
闹得很紧张
between you and General Braegher.
见解不同
Difference in approach.
我们不会疏散哥伦比亚特区的
We are not going to evacuate the District of Columbia.
我要你明白这一点  无论如何
I want you to understand that. Come what may.
另外我向你保证  凡妮莎
And I promise you this... Vanessa.
等我查明真相
When I find out exactly what has happened,
我会记得这次对话
I'm going to remember this conversation,
我会记得  你选择了隐瞒信息
when you chose to withhold information.
布雷格将军是布洛哈特将军的强烈支持者
General Braegher is a strong supporter of General Brockhart.
他们串通了吗
Did they conspire?
他们是不是想利用恐怖
Did they use... terror...
和此次疏散
and this evacuation
让我输掉这场大选
to cost me this election?
我并不喜欢将军这个人
I'm not a fan of the general...
但这是个严重的指控
but... that's a strong charge,
而且没有任何证据支撑
and there's no proof to support it.
你们这些人最擅长保护的  是彼此
You know, what you people protect best is each other.
艾哈迈迪不久前没了踪迹
We lost Ahmadi a short time ago
我们相信他已经不在大马士革了
and believe he is no longer in Damascus.
当然了
Of course.
你听好了
Now you listen to me...
这就是一次
This was nothing more or less
明明白白的政变未遂
than an attempted coup, plain and simple.
我不知道你直接参与的程度多深
And I do not know to what degree you have been directly involved.
但你必须化解它
But you will resolve it.
立即化解
Now.
听明白了吗
Do I make myself clear?
明白了  先生
Yes, sir.
卡车找到了
The truck's been found.
我们还不确定
Now we can't know for sure,
但似乎哈里发国没有参与其中
but it looks as though ICO wasn't involved.
辐照器和铯都已找到
The irradiators and cesium were accounted for.
卡车偶然停在了
The truck was accidentally parked
达勒姆的一处医疗设备厂
at a medical device factory in Durham.
工头没有上报
The plant foreman never reported it.
所以我们暂时可以松口气了
So we can relax for now, at least.
感谢大家的付出  谢谢你们
I just wanna thank you all for your efforts. Thank you.
总统女士  我明天一早就递交辞呈
Madam President. You'll have my resignation in the morning.
诺拉
Nora...
今天这是极端情况
these were extraordinary circumstances today.
如果我们丝毫不容忍人为疏忽
What would our administration be
那我们政府成什么了
if we didn't allow for some human failings?
准备发布会  我们马上上去
Get the presser going. We're coming up now.
关于艾哈迈迪
Concerning Ahmadi...
我们没找到他
We didn't find him.
会找到的  你们可以的
You will. You can.
-你有什么提议  -我可以帮忙
- What are you offering? - Help.
如果您愿意  总统女士
If you'd like it, Madam President.
你能详细说明一下今天早些时候的演习吗
Can you elaborate on the drill earlier today?
演习时常进行
Well, drills happen all the time.
这是政府为了保证国家安全
It's part of the administration's ongoing efforts
做的不懈努力
to keep the country safe.
-是  但通常都会提前提醒  -那意义何在
- Yes, but there's usually a warning. - What's the point of that?
-下一位  -赛斯
- Who's next? - Seth.
你看档案了吗
Did you look at the file?
不用看
I didn't have to.
我希望一小时内
I'll expect your signature
收到你签名的辞职信
on the resignation letter within the hour.
除非你选择指出其他涉事的人
Unless you choose to implicate whoever else was involved.
你不配入主白宫
You don't deserve to be in the White House.
你和你丈夫都不配
Neither you nor your husband.
我本想祝你一切安好  但我觉得你不需要
I'd wish you the best, but I don't think you'll need it.
我相当确定你在私人机构也能干得很好
I'm fairly certain you'll do very well in the private sector.
我安排了周末跟简·戴维斯的会面
I've scheduled a meeting with Jane Davis for the end of the week.
很好
Good.
还有  我之前就想说的
Also, I was going to mention this earlier,
凯茜对艾丹·麦卡伦非常好奇
but Cathy's been very curious about Aidan Macallan.
我已经转移了她的视线  但...
I've thrown her off the scent, but...
凯茜不是问题  而是麦卡伦
Cathy's not the problem. The problem is Macallan,
还有那个纵容麦卡伦成为问题的人
and the person who allowed Macallan to become the problem.
基金募集到了超过了八万
The foundation's raised over 80K.
安东尼于2016年3月15日进入1类捐赠名单
Anthony became status one on the donor list on March 15th, 2016.
莫雷蒂说那是她生命的最后一天
Moretti talked about it as, uh, the last day of her life
之后又改了口
before she corrected herself.
还有  时时刻刻陪着孩子
What else, spent every spare second with the kids.
他们还组装卡丁车来着
They were building a go-kart.
本来就要完成了
They were pretty close to done.
-好吧  -还有呢
- Okay. - I got more.
-不用  我知道了  -你本想知道什么
- No, I got it. - What were you looking for?
没什么
It's nothing.
-好吧  -怎么了
- Okay. - What?
你打算告诉我今天白宫发生了什么吗
You wanna tell me what happened in the White House today?
不打算
No, I don't.
好吧  我一直等着跟你说点事
All right, I've been waiting to say something,
可我等得不想再等了
but I've waited and I don't want to wait anymore.
帮我留意下白宫的工作吧  在新闻部
Consider me for a job at the White House, in comms.
"去拿这个  帮我找那个  我要这个"
"Go get this. Find me that. I need this."
我受够了
I'm tired of it.
你不提出  就会被人命令
If you don't ask, you get asked.
我开始意识到这点了
That's what I'm starting to realize.
我会帮你推荐的
I'll put a word in.
是吗  这话什么意思
Yeah? Well, what does that mean?
意思是时机合适的话  我会提及你
It means that when the moment is right, I'll mention you.
没错  最终宣布后
Yes, whenever it happens...
这次任命便能打破最高法院的僵局
this appointment would break the court's deadlock
我们终于能继续推进这次大选了
and we would get this election going again.
但请大家退一步想一想
But let's step back a minute...
-田纳西州...  -你的盐呢
- Tennessee... - Where's your salt?
-无论谁赢下田州  -水池右边
- Whoever wins that state... - Right side of the sink.
这样就取决于最后一个州
It's come down to one state:
俄亥俄州
Ohio.
一个州的选择  将左右
One state is about to choose
下一任美国总统的人选
the next President of these United States.
那真是演习吗
Was it really a drill?
这届政府一贯喜欢搞闭门政治
This is an administration that operates behind closed doors.
知道吗  今天发生了那么多事
You know, with everything that was happening today,
《先驱报》还来了一个记者
this reporter from the Herald came by.
什么
What?
他想写东尼和基金的报道
Wants to do a story on Tony and the foundation.
他叫什么
What was his name?
戴维斯暗示她能帮我们找到艾哈迈迪
Davis implied she could help us track down Ahmadi.
我觉得我们该听听她要说什么
I think we should hear what she has to say.
她有一种气质  对吧
She's got a quality about her, doesn't she?
令人着迷又害怕
Attractive and terrifying.
就像想抚摸红尾狐的冲动
Like the urge to pet a red tail fox.
将军递交辞呈了吗
The general offered his letter?
是的  但拒绝供出其他人
Uh, he did. And refused to implicate anyone.
你说得对  克莱尔  我们得和厄舍谈谈
You were right, Claire. We need to sit down with Usher.
他这周末正好要去北加州
Just so happens, he's going to Northern California this weekend
见一帮人
to meet with a group of men
讨论我们国家的危机和未来
to discuss the crisis and the future of our country.
-你得受邀才能参加  -对  找他帮忙
- Well, you need to be invited to that. - Yes, let's get him in.
我知道这很显然  但那总让我受触动
I know it's obvious, but it always strikes me.
没有女人
No women.
那个时代不一样
Well, it was a different time.
真可怕
Terrible.
战争还是时代的局限性
The war or the restrictions of the era?
都是
Both.
你知道我的态度
Well, you know my position.
我完全支持女性参战
I'm all for women in combat.
虚惊一场
False alarm...
我很担心你
I was worried about you.
我一直都担心你  克莱尔
I worry about you all the time, Claire.
但我知道你不喜欢听这种话
But I know that's not the kind of thing you like to hear.
马克  进来
Mark. Come in.
-我们有很多要谈  -总统女士
- We have much to discuss. - Madam President.
总统先生
Mr. President.
我确信你知道
As I believe you know,
我们昨天在白宫进行了演习
yesterday we had something of a drill here in the White House.
我知道大家都在好奇怎么回事
I know people are wondering what that was about.
是啊  除了你
Yes. Everyone except you.
本森法官的休会任命宣布仪式
The announcement of the recess appointment of Judge Benson
已经改到明天上午了
has been rescheduled for tomorrow morning.
很好  那...
Good. So...
我们可以进行选举了
we have an election.
但你别想再靠所谓的
Which you will not be able to win
大选期间  在十月逆转竞选局势的现象
"十月惊喜"赢得选举
with another so-called October surprise.
-十月早就过了  -确实
- Well, we are way past October. - We certainly are.
据我所知艾哈迈德·艾哈迈迪仍有威胁
I understand Ahmed Al Ahmadi is still a threat?
是  但你也知道  他神出鬼没
Yes, but he's so elusive, as you know.
很可惜你没能抓到他
It's a shame you weren't able to capture him.
好吧
Well...
我相信机会
I believe that the opportunity
会自己跑到下任总统手中
will present itself to the next president,
无论总统是谁
whomever he may be.
如果威尔·康威胜选
If Will Conway wins the office,
我可以向你保证那会成为当务之急
I can assure you that'll be a top priority.
这恐怖氛围得停止了
This terror has got to stop.
我已经占用你们太多时间了
I've taken enough of your time.
马克  我想放点东西给你听
Mark, I just want to play something for you.
只要一会儿
It'll only take a moment.
我对天发誓
I swear to God,
要是安德伍德往边境派兵
if Underwood puts soldiers on those borders,
我第一个站出来让军人抗命
I'll be the first to tell them not to listen.
如果美国总统下达那种命令
If the President of the United States gives orders like that,
你就让他早死...
you put him out of his--
行  不必再听了
Okay. I don't need to hear anymore.
但  马克
Oh, but, Mark...
后面更精彩
it gets so much better.
美国总统  最高法院大法官  国会议员  都有自己藏身的秘密地堡
最初的地堡被认为是在富兰克林·罗斯福时期建造的
在冷战时  艾森豪威尔总统在国会协助下修建了更多的地堡
这些足以抵御核武器袭击的秘密地堡  其数量  地点均属于国家机密
但几十年来  媒体不断搜集蛛丝马迹  确认应该有40个左右这样的地堡
大部分位于首都华盛顿周围100英里内的山区
这些地堡除了异常坚固之外  有的面积也非常大  可以临时充作空军基地
白宫作战室位于白宫西厢的地下室
而用于藏身的总统紧急行动中心(PEOC)则位于东厢的生活区下面
2011年奥巴马在任时期  椭圆办公室后院曾大兴土木
对外称是空调及电路维修  但很多媒体猜测可能是在扩建地堡